<resources>
    <string name="app_name">BaillieMaweu</string>
    <string name="healthy_recipes">
Healthy Recipes  \n

1. Fruit Salad \n
A mix of fresh fruits like bananas, apples, and oranges. A mix of fresh fruits like bananas, apples, and oranges. A mix of fresh fruits like bananas, apples, and oranges. A mix of fresh fruits like bananas, apples, and oranges. \n\n\n

2. Grilled Chicken \n
Low-fat grilled chicken served with vegetables. \n\n\n

3. Vegetable Stir Fry  \n
Carrots, broccoli, and peppers cooked lightly.  \n\n\n

4. Oatmeal Breakfast  \n
Oats with milk and fruits.  \n\n\n

5. Avocado Toast \n
Whole grain bread topped with avocado.  \n\n\n

6. Boiled Eggs  \n
Rich in protein and easy to prepare. \n\n\n

7. Smoothie Bowl \n
Blended fruits with yogurt and nuts.  \n\n\n

8. Brown Rice and Beans  \n
Healthy and full of fiber.  \n\n\n

9. Baked Fish  \n
Fish baked with lemon and spices.  \n\n\n

10. Greek Yogurt with Honey  \n
Good for digestion and very nutritious. \n\n\n
</string>

    <string name="nutrition">
Nutrition Advice \n\n

1. Fruit Salad \n
A mix of fresh fruits like bananas, apples, and oranges. Great for vitamins, minerals, and fiber.\n\n\n

2. Grilled Chicken \n
Low-fat grilled chicken served with vegetables. Excellent source of lean protein.\n\n\n

3. Vegetable Stir Fry \n
Carrots, broccoli, and peppers cooked lightly. Packed with antioxidants and fiber.\n\n\n

4. Oatmeal Breakfast \n
Oats with milk and fruits. Supports heart health and keeps you full.\n\n\n

5. Avocado Toast \n
Whole grain bread topped with avocado. Rich in healthy fats and fiber.\n\n\n

6. Boiled Eggs \n
Rich in protein and easy to prepare. Helps muscle growth and brain function.\n\n\n

7. Smoothie Bowl \n
Blended fruits with yogurt and nuts. Provides protein, vitamins, and probiotics.\n\n\n

8. Brown Rice and Beans \n
Healthy and full of fiber. Great combination of complex carbs and protein.\n\n\n

9. Baked Fish \n
Fish baked with lemon and  spices. Excellent omega-3 fatty acids source.\n\n\n

10. Greek Yogurt with Honey \n
Good for digestion and very nutritious. Rich in protein and probiotics.\n\n\n

11. Almonds \n
A handful of almonds daily. Supports heart health and keeps you energized.\n\n\n

12. Spinach Salad \n
Spinach, cherry tomatoes, cucumbers, and olive oil. High in iron and vitamins.\n\n\n

13. Quinoa Bowl \n
Quinoa with vegetables and chickpeas. Complete protein with fiber.\n\n\n

14. Cottage Cheese \n
Low-fat cottage cheese with fruits. High protein and calcium.\n\n\n

15. Lentil Soup \n
Warm lentil soup with spices. Excellent source of plant protein and fiber.\n\n\n

16. Berries Mix \n
Blueberries, raspberries, and strawberries. Rich in antioxidants and vitamins.\n\n\n

17. Sweet Potato \n
Baked sweet potato. High in fiber and vitamin A.\n\n\n

18. Chia Pudding \n
Chia seeds soaked in milk or yogurt. Rich in omega-3s and fiber.\n\n\n

19. Turkey Wrap \n
Whole wheat wrap with turkey and veggies. Lean protein and complex carbs.\n\n\n

20. Green Tea\n
Unsweetened green tea. Boosts metabolism and rich in antioxidants.\n\n\n
</string>
    <string name="meditation">
       Meditation Activity \n\n
       1. When you meditate you relax your mind. \n
        You can meditate my exercising regularly. \n
        Meditation enables someone to free their mind from the struggles their are going through.\n
        Meditation is one of the ways one can relieve stress.\n
        Meditation can be done in many ways.\n
        Apart from exercising one can do Yoga.\n

    </string>

    <string name="hydration">
        Welcome to hydration Activity \n\n
        You need to drink enough water \n
        It is good for your health \n\n
        2. Ensure the water is clean \n
        The water must be clean \n\n
        3. Staying hydrated saves you \n
        It prevents you from having diseases such as kidney failure \n\n
        4. Hydration protects your skin \n
        It strengthens your skin and makes your skin to be clear.\n\n
    </string>

    <string name="exercise">
        Welcome to Exercise Activity \n\n
        1. Exercise is one of the essentials that one has to add in there to do list .\n
        2.When one does not exercise they are slowly killing themselves.
        This is because exercise they not only strengthen their body but also improve their immune system.\n
        3.Thus one should occasionally exercise
    </string>

    <string name="motivation">
        Welcome to Motivation Activity\n\n
        1.One should motivate themselves to live a healthy life \n
        This is because it will enable them to live longer.\n

        2. One should reward himself\n
        When one follows his /her healthy routine her should motivate himself in a healthy manner.\n

        3 One should punish himself\n
        When one fails to keep up with their program they should punish themselves in order not to redo the mistake.

    </string>


    <string name="Weeklygoals">
        Welcome to weekly Goals Activity \n\n\n
        Here we help you create a weekly program of maintaining good health.\n
        We help you create a good routine for yourself.\n
        This depends on How much weight you want to lose, You budget on what you it and how much freetime you have or your exercise time.\n

    </string>

    <string name="Progress">
        Welcome to Progress Activity\n\n\n
        Here we are able to see the progress that you have made.
        We achieve this by tracking your exercise time using our app which can be connected to your smart watch.\n
        We also ask you to fill a questionnaire on how you are doing, This is done weekly.\n
        We also award those who are able to follow their routine to the latter.
    </string>
</resources>